https://leadertec.com/our-privacy-policy/

Fishing knots
Knots for forming double lines:
Bimini twist
Australian Plait or Braid
Spider hitch
Knots for tying swivels and hooks:
Return knot
Knots for joining swivel to double line:
Offshore Swivel knot (Cat’s paw)
Improved Clinch knot
Uni knot
Palomar knot
Berkley Trilene knot
Knots for forming loops:
Surgeon’s loop knot
Leader loop knot
Perfection loop knot
Offshore loop knot (Flemish eye)
Knots for joining heavy leader to lighter main line:
Fisherman’s bend / Double Uni knot
Knots for joining two lines of similar diameter:
Leader knot
Fisherman’s bend / Double Uni knot
Blood knot
Fisherman’s bend variation
Miscellaneous knots:
Cow hitch (Lark’s head knot)
Fishing knots
Knots for forming double lines:
Bimini twist
Australian Plait or Braid
Spider hitch
Knots for tying swivels and hooks:
Return knot
Knots for joining swivel to double line:
Offshore Swivel knot (Cat’s paw)
Improved Clinch knot
Uni knot
Palomar knot
Berkley Trilene knot
Knots for forming loops:
Surgeon’s loop knot
Leader loop knot
Perfection loop knot
Offshore loop knot (Flemish eye)
Knots for joining heavy leader to lighter main line:
Fisherman’s bend / Double Uni knot
Knots for joining two lines of similar diameter:
Leader knot
Fisherman’s bend / Double Uni knot
Blood knot
Fisherman’s bend variation
Miscellaneous knots:
Cow hitch (Lark’s head knot)
Privacy Statement
Our privacy policy is very simple. We value our privacy, and we know that you do too. We never pass on any of our customers details to any other company. If you wish to receive our occasional newsletter with information that we feel may be of interest, you can sign up for it and that’s all you will ever receive from us. Remember that you can unsubscribe at any time.
Cookies in use on this site and how they benefit you
A cookie is a small file of letters and numbers that we put on your computer if you agree. The information that is collected by cookies on our website is used to analyse the use of our website to help guide improvements and to improve functionality of our website. We also use certain tracking cookies, some of which link to social networking sites like Twitter and these may contain information personal to the individual visitor. By using our website, you agree that we can place these types of cookies on your device.
Our cookies help us:
Make our website work as you’d expect
Save you having to login every time you visit the site
Remember your settings during and between visits
Improve the speed/security of the site
Allow you to share pages with social networks like Facebook
Personalise our site to you to help you get what you need faster
Continuously improve our website for you
Make our marketing more efficient (ultimately helping us to offer the service we do at the price we do)
We do not use cookies to:
Collect any personally identifiable information (without your express permission)
Collect any sensitive information (without your express permission)
Pass personally identifiable data to third parties
You can learn more about all the cookies we use below
Granting us permission to use cookies
If the settings on your software that you are using to view this website (your browser) are adjusted to accept cookies we take this, and your continued use of our website, to mean that you are fine with this. Should you wish to remove or not use cookies from our site you can learn how to do this below, however doing so will likely mean that our site will not work as you would expect.
How to control and delete cookies
You can block or restrict the use of cookies through your browser settings. For more information on cookies, their use and blocking them you may want to visit www.aboutcookies.org
List of the main cookies used on this website
Website Function
Cookies
Our own cookies
We use cookies to make our website work including:
Making our shopping basket and checkout work
Determining if you are logged in or not
Remembering your search settings
Allowing you to add comments to our site
Tailoring content to your needs
There is no way to prevent these cookies being set other than to not use our site.
Third party functions
Our site, like most websites, includes functionality provided by third parties. Disabling these cookies will likely break the functions offered by these third parties
Social Website Cookies
So you can easily ‘Like’ or share our content on the likes of Facebook and Twitter we have included sharing buttons on our site.
Cookies are set by:
AddThis – provide us with lots of sharing buttons all in one neat package
The privacy implications on this will vary from social network to social network and will be dependent on the privacy settings you have chosen on these networks.
Visitor Statistics Cookies
We use cookies to compile visitor statistics such as how many people have visited our website, what type of technology they are using (e.g. Mac or Windows which helps to identify when our site isn’t working as it should for particular technologies), how long they spend on the site, what page they look at etc. This helps us to continuously improve our website. These so called ‘analytics’ programs also tell us if how people reached this site (e.g. from a search engine) and whether they have been here before helping us to put more money into developing our services for you instead of marketing spend.
We use: Statcounter and Google Analytics
We accept payment by Visa and Mastercard and you can order online
using our secure server provided by Worldpay Plc , one of the largest
internet payment processors in the world. You can also pay using
Paypal; the online store will transfer you to the Paypal secure
website to complete the transaction if this option is selected.
This site and all contents are ©2005-2020 Leadertec Ltd
sales@leadertec.com
Registered in England, Company No. 4120402
Home
TACKLESTORE
RIGGING ACCESSORIES
LURE RIGGING ACCESSORIES
ANTI CHAFE GEAR
Contact Us
This website uses cookies to improve your experience. We'll assume you're ok with this, but you can opt-out if you wish. Cookie settingsACCEPTPrivacy & Cookies Policy
Close
Privacy Overview
This website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these cookies, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may have an effect on your browsing experience.
Necessary
Always Enabled
Necessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. This category only includes cookies that ensures basic functionalities and security features of the website. These cookies do not store any personal information.
Non-necessary
Non-necessary
Any cookies that may not be particularly necessary for the website to function and is used specifically to collect user personal data via analytics, ads, other embedded contents are termed as non-necessary cookies. It is mandatory to procure user consent prior to running these cookies on your website.
Select your currency
GBP
Pound sterling
EUREuro
USD
United States (US) dollar
Login / My account
Shipping Details
